Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2460)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2461)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2462)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2463)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2464)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2465)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2466)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2467)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2468)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2469)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2470)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2471)
  - Portrait of Edgar Paxson, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2472)
  - Portrait of Edgar Paxson, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2473)
  - Rodeo, undated; Same photo as 82-0251; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2474)
  - Portrait of Edgar Paxson, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2475)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2476)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2477)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2478)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2479)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2480)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2481)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2482)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2483)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2484)
  - World War I photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2485)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2486)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2487)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2488)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2489)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2490)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2491)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2492)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2493)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2494)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2495)
  - House construction, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2496)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2497)
  - Camping, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2498)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway Locomotive#272, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2499)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2500)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2501)
  - Townspeople of Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2502)
  - Prize fight in Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2503)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2504)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2505)
  - Prize fight in Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2506)
  - Townspeople of Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2507)
  - Townspeople of Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2508)
  - Prize fight in Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2509)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2510)
  - Prize fight in Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2511)
  - Prize fight in Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2512)
  - Townspeople of Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2513)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2514)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2515)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2516)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2517)
  - Prize fight in Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2518)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2519)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2520)
  - Townspeople of Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2521)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2522)
  - Taft, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2523)
  - Animals in a stockyard/pen, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2524)
  - School Days, yearbook photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2525)
  - School Days, yearbook photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2526)
  - School Days, yearbook photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2527)
  - Children in front of schoolhouse, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2528)
  - Aerial, Missoula, Montana (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2529)
  - Railroad trestle bridge, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2530)
  - Railroad tracks, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2531)
  - Railroad tunnel, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2532)
  - Person on a porch, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2533)
  - Flood of 1908, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2534)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2535)
  - Power house, Bonner Dam, Bonner, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2536)
  - Northern Pacific Railway locomotive and engineers, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2537)
  - Greenough Park, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2538)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Depot, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2539)
  - Greenough Park, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2540)
  - Greenough Park, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2541)
  - Hell Gate, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2542)
  - School Days, yearbook photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2543)
  - School Days, yearbook photos, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2544)
  - Mount Jumbo, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2545)
  - The Best in Montana, Missoula basketball team yearbook spread, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2546)
  - Senior Actors, yearbook spread, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2547)
  - Native Americans in Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2548)
  - Flood or fire damage (?), undated; Same photo as 76-2335 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2549)
  - Flood or fire damage (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2550)
  - Fire's destruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2551)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2552)
  - Missoula fire department chiefs, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2553)
  - Fourth of July Parade, corner of East Pine and Jefferson Streets, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2554)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2555)
  - Group of people surrounding dead horses on the ground (?), undated; Same photo as 76-0297; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2556)
  - Charles F. Buls family home (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2557)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2558)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2559)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2560)
  - Butte fire department wagon parked in front of Bottick and McCurdy's Queen City Saloon and Hollands Restaurant, Butte, Montana, undated; Same as photo 76-0276 (umt010889); larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2561)
  - Parade, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2562)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2563)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2564)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2565)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2566)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2567)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2568)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2569)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2570)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2571)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2572)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2573)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2574)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2575)
  - Missoula's newspaper headlines, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2576)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2577)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2578)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2579)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2580)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2581)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2582)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2583)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2584)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2585)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2586)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2587)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2588)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2589)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, January 30, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2590)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, January 30, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2591)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, January 30, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2592)
  - Greenough Mansion water closet, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2593)
  - Greenough Mansion water closet, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2594)
  - Greenough Mansion water closet, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2595)
  - Greenough Mansion water closet, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2596)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2597)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2598)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2599)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2600)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2601)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2602)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2603)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2604)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2605)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2606)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2607)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2608)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2609)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2610)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2611)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2612)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2613)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2614)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2615)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2616)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2617)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2618)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2619)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2620)
  - Aerial views of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2621)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2622)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2623)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2624)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2625)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2626)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2627)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2628)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2629)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2630)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2631)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2632)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2633)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2634)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2635)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2636)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2637)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2638)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2639)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2640)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2641)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2642)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2643)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2644)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2645)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2646)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2647)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2648)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2649)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2650)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2651)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion roof, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2652)
  - Aerial view of Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2653)
  - Aerial view of Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2654)
  - Aerial view of Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2655)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2656)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2657)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2658)
  - Putting Greenough Mansion together, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2659)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, January 30, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2660)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, January 30, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2661)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, January 30, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2662)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2663)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2664)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2665)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2666)
  - Aerial views of University of Montana and Campbell Field, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2667)
  - Aerial view of Clark Fork at Higgins Avenue and Orange Street, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2668)
  - Aerial view of Clark Fork at Higgins Avenue and Orange Street, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2669)
  - Aerial view of Clark Fork at Higgins Avenue and Orange Street, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2670)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2671)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2672)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2673)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2674)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2675)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2676)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2677)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2678)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2679)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2680)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2681)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2682)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2683)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2684)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2685)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2686)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2687)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2688)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2689)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2690)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2691)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2692)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2693)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2694)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2695)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2696)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2697)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2698)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2699)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2700)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2701)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2702)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2703)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2704)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2705)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2706)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2707)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2708)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2709)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2710)
  - Mosby and his mansion before move, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2711)
  - Aerial view near Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2712)
  - Aerial view near Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2713)
  - Aerial view near Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2714)
  - Aerial view near Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2715)
  - Aerial view near Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2716)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's valley, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2717)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's valley, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2718)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's valley, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2719)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2720)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2721)
  - Aerial view of Missoula's airport, September 7, 1968 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2722)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2723)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2724)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2725)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2726)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2727)
  - Framework supporting Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2728)
  - Framework supporting Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2729)
  - Framework supporting Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2730)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2731)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2732)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2733)
  - Moving Greenough Mansion, Fall 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2734)
  - Evaro train wreck, June 10, 1962 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4175)
  - Evaro train wreck, June 10, 1962 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4176)
  - Evaro train wreck, June 10, 1962 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4177)
  - Lolo Hot Springs, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4435)
  - Lolo Hot Springs, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4436)
  - Lolo Hot Springs, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4437)
  - Lolo Hot Springs, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4438)
  - Lolo Hot Springs, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4439)
  - Lolo Hot Springs, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4440)
  - Polley's Lumber Company train, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4441)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway Company Depot, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4442)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway Company Depot, Missoula, Montana, 1920s (Box 7, Photo number 94-4443)
  - Prize fight, Taft, Montana, 1908; Photographer: H. English (Box 7, Photo number 94-4444)
  - Prize fight, Taft, Montana, 1908; Photographer: H. English (Box 7, Photo number 94-4445)
  - Prize fight, Taft, Montana, 1908; Photographer: H. English (Box 7, Photo number 94-4446)
  - Loading lumber at Taft, Montana, 1908; Photographer: H. English (Box 7, Photo number 94-4447)
  - Main Street Taft, Montana, 1908; Photographer: H. English (Box 7, Photo number 94-4448)
  - Main Street Taft, Montana, 1908; Photographer: H. English (Box 7, Photo number 94-4449)
  - Hot Springs, Montana, Main Street, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4668)
  - Hot Springs, Montana, bath house, undated (Box 7, Photo number 94-4669)
  - Northwest corner of Pine Street and Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, circa 1930 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4670)
  - Mail plane at Hale Field, Missoula, Montana, circa 1930 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4671)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Depot, Missoula, Montana, circa 1930 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4672)
  - Elks building, northeast corner, Pattee and Front Streets, Missoula, Montana, circa 1939 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4673)
  - Race car at Missoula County Fair Grounds, Missoula, Montana, circa 1930 (Box 7, Photo number 94-4674)